ati.com 2005-12-10

# Privacy Policy

  | 

_Last updated June 28, 2005._

**We take your privacy seriously. We are committed to protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about you. It remains our policy and our commitment not to distribute, sell, rent or in any way make available your name, email address or other personal information to any third party without your prior written consent.**

We also recognize that our visitors, and the parents of children visiting our site, need protection of any personally identifying information they choose to share with us. This privacy policy is intended to provide you with the information on how we collect, use and store the information that you provide, so that you can make appropriate choices for sharing information with us. 

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our privacy statement or policies, please contact:

Attention: Director, ATI Internet Marketing & Development  
ATI Technologies, Inc.  
55 Commerce Valley Drive West  
Markham, Ontario, L3T 7V9, Canada   
Telephone: (905) 882-2600  
Fax: (905) 882-6099  
E-Mail: [privacy@ati.com](mailto:privacy@ati.com)  

**The following sections will cover:**

  * **Websites we operate**
  * **Information we collect from you**
  * **ATI’s use of Personal Information**
  * **Control of your Personal Information**
  * **Security of your Personal Information**
  * **Use of Cookies**
  * **Web Beacons**
  * **Spotlight Tags**
  * **Parental Consent **
  * **Parental Access**
  * **Enforcement of this Statement**
  * **Changes to this Statement**

**Websites we operate  
** We currently operate the web sites www.ati.com and www.shopati.com (the (“Sites”). In addition, we own several other domain names that point to the web sites listed above. From time to time we may add new sites that may not be listed above, but will provide a link to this policy.

**Information We Collect From You  
**In order to operate the Sites and provide you with information on products and services that may be of interest to you, we may collect contact information (i.e., information that could be used to contact you, such as full name, postal address, phone number and email address, as well as your computer’s unique IP address (if any)), financial information (i.e., passwords, credit card numbers and bank and other financial institution account numbers) and demographic information (e.g., zip code, hometown, gender, purchase history information and age as well as IP addresses that are not unique to your computer) from you. Please note that nowhere on the Sites do we knowingly collect contact information or financial information from children under the age of 13.

**ATI's Use of Personal Information  
**ATI will ask for your consent when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are asked to register before entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site, or when purchasing and registering ATI products. Personal information collected by ATI often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested. 

When you buy and install a new product, we ask you to register your purchase electronically. When you do, we keep this registration information on file (in our secure database) with any information you've already given us on previous visits to our Sites. This is considered your personal information. 

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited, by contract, from using that information for any other purpose. 

ATI will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process served on ATI or the Sites; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of ATI and its Sites, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Sites, or the public.

**Control of your Personal Information**  
You may unsubscribe from emails and promotional offers by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email sent to you by ATI, or by changing your preference on your ATI Communication Preference Center Profile. 

If your email address has changed and you would like to continue to receive the ati.com newsletter(s), you will need update your profile with your new email address. 

ATI.com may, if you choose to receive them, send out periodic emails informing you of technical service issues, information about account issues, or news about changes or updates to the site. As long as you maintain an ati.com account, you can choose to opt-in or opt-out of these emails.

**Security of your Personal Information  
** ATI Technologies Inc. is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of advanced security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on secured computer servers that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

All or most data received through ATI’s online product registration form is collected by ATI Technologies Inc. and is housed with it’s out sourced service provider Parature Inc. in the United States of America. All personal information is encrypted during data transfer and stored using a variety of advanced security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Your personal information will never be shared or sold to any third party organization without your express consent. Personal information will only collected, stored and used from persons who are thirteen years of age or older.

A password is required to access your ati.com or your ShopATI.com account. It is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always choose to log out before leaving your ati.com account to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

**Use of Cookies  
** This Web site uses cookies to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a **small** text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page, so that when you visit the site again, the experience will be personalized. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. 

If you choose to set your computer to accept cookies, you may **also** choose to be automatically logged into the ATI.com Customer Care portal. Your selection is stored in a cookie. 

The ati.com Customer Care portal also makes use of session cookies (also called a “transient cookie”). Session cookies are stored in temporary memory and erased when you close your web browser. Session cookies do not collect information from your computer. The session cookie is used to present relevant self-help information based on your ATI Customer Care profile (for registered users).

We may use cookies to:

  * Keep count of your return visits to our site or our clients' sites 
  * Accumulate and report anonymous, aggregate, statistical information on web site usage 
  * Deliver content specific to your interests 
  * Save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites. 

******Web Beacons**  
ATI uses HBX and HitBox web analytics services which contain electronic image requests (called a "single-pixel gif" or "web beacon" request). We include web beacons in HTML-formatted newsletters that we send to opt-in subscribers in order to count how many newsletters have been read. Our web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor or share any personal information about our web site visitors, they are just the technique we use to compile our anonymous information about web site usage.

******Spotlight Tags**  
ATI Technologies Inc. uses third party advertising companies for banner placements who in turn use pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partner. These files enable our ad management partner to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie is placed by us and our ad management partner who works with DoubleClick. With both cookies and Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy>

**Parental Consent  
**In order for children under 13 years old to participate in online activities that require registration, we require prior written permission from a parent or guardian (opt-in). A parental consent form is available at <http://www.ati.com/companyinfo/legal/consent.html>. This form must be signed by the child's parent or guardian and returned to 

Attention: ATI Internet Marketing & Development  
ATI Technologies, Inc.  
55 Commerce Valley Drive West  
Markham, Ontario, L3T 7V9, Canada   
Telephone: (905) 882-2600  
Fax: (905) 882-6099  

Once we have obtained parental consent, we only ask the child for information that is reasonably necessary for the child to participate in our online activities. 

**Parental Access  
**A parent who has given ATI Technologies Inc. permission to collect his or her child's information can, at any time, do the following: (1) confirm, correct or have deleted the child's personal information; (2) discontinue further use of the child's information and/or communication with the child; and/or, (3) revoke his or her earlier consent to collect and use the child's information. To update your child’s profile please complete the following form [http://www.ati.com/companyinfo/legal/consent_form.html ](http://www.ati.com/companyinfo/legal/consent_form.html)and we will review or update your child's information as appropriate. Please be sure to include in your fax or email the email address your child used to register.

**Enforcement of this Statement  
** If you have questions regarding this Statement, you should first contact [privacy@ati.com](mailto:privacy@ati.com). In most cases we respond to your inquiries within a 24-hour time period. 

**Changes to this Statement ati.com** will occasionally update this Privacy Statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the Privacy Statement. For material changes to this Statement, ATI will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement to be informed of how ATI Technologies Inc. is helping to protect your information.

|
